Guide to the James E. Dyer Papers MS 052
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- Series II: WestConn Materials, RG6.xx___x
  - Post-WCSC - Pre-Mayoral Scrapbook, 1971-1976 (Box OS 12)
    WCSC Groundbreaking and luncheon 4/4/74
    E12Memorial Day 5/74
    Danbury Democratic Picnic
    Ella Grasso and JD 8/25/74
    Danbury fall '74 by JD
    Fifth District Young Democrats, winter 1975
    JD and Chris Dodd 1975
    Ron Pagano Yearbook Editor w/JD and Ruth Haas 10/1975
    "Nixron in '76" campaign
    Commencement Jan.1976
    JD with Robert Bersi, students, WCSC Commencement 1976
    Young Democrats State Convention, Bridgeport 5/8/76
    JD 1976 Campaign
    Yearbook Office 1974?
    "Vette 1" 1971 Corvette Stingray)
  - Yearbook photographs, 1972 (Box 39.1, Folder 5)
    Two 5x7 b/w
- Series III: Political and Professional Career, RG6.xx___x
  - Subseries A: Audio and Video, RG6.xx___x
    - RFK Dinner, Opening Remarks by Morris Udall (Arizona), Sonesta, Hartford, CT, March 7, 1975 (Box 23)
    - State Representative campaign ads (reel to reel), 1976 (Box 91, Folder Reel/Reel)
    - Graduation 1/2/1977 (Box 23)
    - Kick-Off Rally Sept. 20, 1978; Abate-Dempsey (Box 23)
    - JD speeches, election, swearing in, and mayoral debate Oct.18, 1979 (reel to reel) (Box 91)
    - The Barry Grey Program 12/1/1981 (Box 23)
    - JD Ads (copyright 1981) (Box 23)
    - Dyer vs. Boughton, WLAD Radio 10/16/1981 (Box 23)
    - Danbury Democratic Town Committee Radio Ads WLAD, duplicate tape (reel to reel), 1981 (Box 91)
    - Dyer - Carbide Xplo (Explosion), 1982 (Box 23)
    - Year End Review WiNE, 1982 (Box 23)
    - Year End Review WLAD, 1982 (Box 23)
    - Ethan Allen Inn, 8/2/1982, 1983 (Box 23)
    - Year End Review WiNE, 1983 (Box 23)
    - Year End Review WLAD, 1984 (Box 23)
    - Year End Review WiNE, 1984 (Box 23)
    - Dyer for Mayor, 2 - thirty second spots (reel to reel), undated (Box 91, Folder Reel/Reel)
    - Danbury Democrats, 4: 30s, cut #1 for WATR, 940 (reel to reel), undated (Box 91, Folder Reel/Reel)
    - "Sunday Supplement" 940 WiNE, 1985 (Box 23)
    - Mayor Dyer Hosts the I-95 Psychedelic Supper, 1985 (Box 23)
    - Dyer '85 2-30 second spots, 1985 (Box 23)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
      1/4" reel to reel
    - WiNE Debate, 1985 (Box 23)
    - Golden Throat Dyer '85 2-20 second spots and WiNE Editorial 10/31/85, 1985 (Box 23)
    - Tues. Nov. 5, 1985 (Given to JD by Wayne Gosselin 1/2/1986) (Box 23)
    - WiNE Year End summary 1985, 1986 (Box 23)
    - Arson in Danbury 9/1/86 - 9/5/86, 1986 (Box 23)
    - 940 WiNE Radio, Jim Dyer '87 (3 spots), 1987 (Box 23)
    - 940 WiNE Radio, Democratic town Committee/Primary (3 spots), 1987 (Box 23)
    - Debate 9/8/1987 (micro cassette tape) (Box 23)
    - Used in 1987 election on WREF and WLAD; 1 - :60 second spot (reel to reel) (Box 91, Folder Reel/Reel)
    - Connecticut Defense Attorneys 6/1/1992 (Box 23)
    - JD/TD on WLAD, undated (Box 23)
    - Dialogue 80, WLAD, 10/1/1993 (Box 23)
  - Subseries B: Photographs, RG6.xx___x
    - Pierre Salinger (8x10 b/w studio portrait), ca.1960 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Groundbreaking for City Hall, Thomas Dyer, Councilman, far right (one 8x10 b/w labeled), 1968 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - John S. Monagan, Rep. 5th District Connecticut; candids campaigning with Hubert H. Humphrey, and studio portrait (One 8x10, one 6x8, three 5x7), ca.1972 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - JD as Congressional Aide In Woodbury Office (one 5x7 b/w), 1972 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Rep. John S. Monagan (contact sheet), ca.1972 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - D.C. Convention to replace Eagleton; Sargent Shriver at podium (two 5x7 b/w), 1972 (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Inaugural Ball/Ella Grasso, JD and AD (one 4x6 color), 1974 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Stewart Udall, posed (one 5x7 and one 8x10 b/w), 1975 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - "NiXRon in '76, fifth district young democrats," Bill Riley, Charlie Covillo, and JD (one 5x7 b/w), 1976 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - "Dyer & Pop" Election Night 11/2/1976 (one 8x10 b/w) (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Donald W. Boughton (one 8x10 b/w), 1977 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - JD as State Representative (9 5x7 and one 4x4 b/w; one 5x7 and one 3.5x4.5 color) Includes "Nahley" contact sheet/negatives 9/4/1978, 1976-1978 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - JD with Ella Grasso (one 8x10 b/w matted), 0000 (Box 38)
    - Ella Signing My Anti-Child Pornography Law 6/78, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Campaign '79, posed (one 3x4 b/w), 1979 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Swearing In and Campaign Photo (one 8x10 b/w), 1979 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Brian Murphy holding election poster (3x4 color framed), 1979 (Box 38)
    - JD in Mayor's Office signing Shriner's Air Show Proclamation (posed) 11x14 color on board, 1980 (Box OS 11)
    - Mayor's Cup Golf with former Mayors Bowman, DeFine, Dribella, Arconti, Dyer, Boughton (one 8x10 color), 1980 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - AD and Governor O'Neill (one 8x10 b/w), 1981 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Campaign '81 (two 5x7 and seven 8x10 b/w, one 4x5 color), 1981 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - City Scenes by James Reynolds Associates (contact sheets), 1981 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Danbury State Fair: JD Aboard Danbury Fair Train (one 4x6 color photo and Gate Pass), 1981 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Danbury State Fair Last Day, October 12, 1981, for Time Magazine (one 8x10 b/w) (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Local Political Events, Columbus Day Dinner, World Trade Week, Democrat Clambake, Melody-Halas Fund, England trip, Eagle Scout Award, (JD, AD, Gov.O'Neill, Mayor Athanson (England), Jayne Holmes, Stephen Feldman (16 various sizes, 3.5x4.25 to 5x7 color and b/w) labeled/unlabeled, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Robert S. Young Library Dedication and Grasso Hall Construction (eight 8x10 b/w), 1982 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Public Utilities (Water) JD with unknown individual, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Local Political Events: Election Day; Swearing In; DAR Luncheon, (JD, AD, Edwin R. Newman, Joseph Leiberman, W.R. Ratchford (26 5x7 b/w and color, one 4x6 color, and six 3.5x5 color) labeled/unlabeled, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 25-26)
    - Aerial City Scenes (one roll b/w negatives), 1983 (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - JD in Mayor's Office, posed (10 various sizes, 3.5x5 to 5x7 color b/w), 1983-1987 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - JD naming Joseph J. Bertalovitz Fire Headquarters and JD w/Gov. O'Neill (two 8x10 b/w), 1983 (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - People"s Bank Opening, Shelter Rock Office, and Union Trust Mill Plain Office (five 5x7 b/w), 1983-1984 (Box 39, Folder 30)
    - Local Political Events (Gouveia, M.Guitar, Ted Mondale, Gov. O'Neill, Pope John Paul II Center for Health Care Dinner-Dance and naming of firehouse (Nine various sizes: 3.5x4.5 to 8x10 b/w and color), 1984-1985 (Box 39, Folder 31)
    - Danbury Fair Mall Groundbreaking, and aerial view (five 8x10 b/w, five 7x10 color, one 8x10 color), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 32)
    - Ives Street Firehouse Conversion to Fitzwilly's Restaurant (12 3.5x5 color), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - Novo Labs (artist's rendition) one 8x10 color, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 34)
    - Tricentennial, AD on Tricentennial float (one 8x8 color and four 3.5x5 b/w w/negatives), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 35)
    - JD and Chris Dodd shaking hands; Wally Lee, Dave Burke, and Betty Crudginton (one 5x7 color matted), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 36)
    - JD Giving Peter Glaser His Degree (two 5x7 color), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 37)
    - Mayor's Office, JD posed at desk and with Rose Kruse, Jackie Cruz and Intern Peter Glaser in Mayor's Office (four 5x7 b/w and one 5x7 color), 1984-1986 (Box 39, Folder 38)
    - Danbury Connecticut HELP US CELEBRATE! 300 Years Great 1684/85 - 1984/85 (one 8x12 color photograph matted), 1984-1986 (Box OS 3)
    - Celebrity Breakfast, JD as waiter (three 8x10 b/w), 1985 (Box 39, Folder 39)
    - City Scenes (24 b/w photographs), 1985 (Box 39, Folder 40)
    - Memorial Day Parade (20x20 color), ca.1985 (Box OS 13)
    - Group photograph with note from Roger W. Kirwood (8x10 color framed), ca.1985 (Box OS 1)
    - Local Political Events: Nomination, Swearing In, Franklin-Osborne Connector; Planting Tree Ceremony, Technipower Anniversary; Tricentennial (JD, AD, Gov.O'Neill,Red Cross,A.Hayman,Paul Garavel,Bill Cutting) 44 various sizes (3.5x5 to 8x10 color and b/w), 1985 (Box 39, Folder 41)
    - North East Governor's Conference in Danbury (four 8x10 b/w), 1985 (Box 39, Folder 42)
    - Presidents Regan, Ford, Carter, Nixon w/note from Jim McNamara (one 8x10 color), 1985 (Box 39, Folder 43)
    - Publicity Photographs by T. J. Judd (23 4x6 and two 2.5x4 b/w), 1985 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Publicity Contact Sheets by T. J. Judd (22 b/w contact sheets), 0000 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Irving Stolberg, Stephen Feldman, and SGA President outside Grasso Hall (one 3.5x5 color), 1985 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Tricentennial, Steve Collins (one 8x10 color matted), 1985 (Box 38)
    - Danbury Fair Mall Opening, JD and Gov. O'Neill (one 5x7 b/w), 1986 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Danbury Fair Mall Opening Night Celebration October 28, 1986: JD with AD and (one 10.5x13.5 b/w framed) (Box OS 1)
    - Danbury Fair Mall Opening Night Celebration October 28, 1986: JD with Gov. O'Neill (one 8x10 b/w matted) (Box 38)
    - Danbury Fair Mall Opening Night Celebration, October 28, 1986: JD and AD (11x14 b/w) (Box 38)
    - Downtown Revelopment (six 4x5 color negatives by T. J. Judd), 1986 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - JD in driver's seat of Connecticut Limousine Service, Inc. vehicle w/unknown individual (8x10 b/w framed), 1986 (Box OS 1)
    - Local Political Events and City Scenes: Memorial Day, Veterans Day, Hands Around Danbury, New DHS Field & Track, Richter Arts Awards, Mary Rickert Retirement, State Convention, Bear Mountain Cottage, Redevelopment, (JD, AD, TJD, Chief Bertakowitz, W.Anderson, J.Cruz, Chris Dodd, and 1986 Lifeguard Champions John Leopold, Tim Minahan, Dave Leopold, Karl Krebs, Leonard Sedney, Keith Colgan) 127 various sizes (8x10 to 3.5x5 b/w and color) (Box 40, Folder 6-10)
    - Mayor's Office JD (three 20x30 color, posed), 1986 (Box OS 13)
    - Post Office Street Construction, Taste of Danbury (three 8x10 and nine 8x11 color), 1986 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Bear Mountain Cottage, Fire House Before and After Renovation, Local Restaurants and Good Neighbor House (12 5x7 color and b/w), 1987 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - JD last day in office, posed (one 8x10 b/w), 1987 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Local Events, 14 various sizes (3.5x5 to 5x7 color and b/w), 1987 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - N.A.S.A. Shuttle landing with sunset in background (one 8x10 color), undated (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - New York City Skyline, Sunrise/Sunset (15x15 mounted on foam core), ca.1990 (Box OS 12)
    - "Waiting for the Verdict" (one 8x10 color), 1991 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Stephen Feldman's Farewell Party (one 4x6 color), 1992 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - JD with George Paschalis (one 5x7 b/w), 1997 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Campaign portrait, 1982 (Box 38)
      Two 8x10, one 5x7 and one 4x5 color portrait
    - JD as Congressional Aide, 1972 (Box 39.1, Folder 6)
      Two 3.5x5 color
    - Ted Kennedy, Sargent Shriver, J. Monagan in Waterbury (photographs by JD), 1972 (Box 39.1, Folder 7)
      Four various sizes mounted on board
    - State Democratic Convention, Jul 1974 (Box 39.1, Folder 8)
      One color slide
    - JD State Representative Campaign (candids/posed), 1976 (Box 39.1, Folder 9)
      28 color slides
    - Miscellaneous events (JD seconding nomination for Ella Grasso, "Dyer" on State House Voting Tally, Jaycees, Columbus Day, Eagle Scout Ceremony, "Connecticut Cooks," Rabbit Hutch Show, Mouner Farah, Sally Estefan, Gov. O'Neill, Chief Macedo, Vespucci dinner, Greek Festival, Bishop Curtis, Portugese Dinner, WCSC, SCSC), 1977-1987 (Box 39.1, Folder 10)
      42 various sizes (3.5x4.5- 5x7 color and b/w photographs)
    - JD with constituents, candids/posed, 1979 (Box 39.1, Folder 11)
      Seven 35mm color slides
    - Official Photograph, posed, 1979-1983 (Box 39.1, Folder 12)
      Two 5x7 and one 4x5 color photographs
    - Miscellaneous publicity photographs: Phil Cappozi, Lou Sedey, Paul Schierloh, Rick Gottschalk, Sandy Salvatore, Tony Yakacki, Danbury Labor Council, school children, Rose Krose, Ted Goldstein, Patsy Spano, Italian Fest, Portugese Festival, Old Firehouse restoration, and the old Library restoration, 1981-1986 (Box 39.1, Folder 13)
      19 5x7 b/w photographs
    - City scenes, Apr 1981 (Box 39.1, Folder 14)
      20 35mm color slides
    - Council meeting, city scenes, firemen, candids/posed, Apr 1981 (Box 39.1, Folder 15)
      40 35mm color slides
    - Mayor's office with school children, May 1981 (Box 39.1, Folder 16)
      12 35mm color slides
    - Swearing In Ceremony (Photographs by James Reynolds Associates), Nov 1981 (Box 39.1, Folder 17)
      One 5x7 b/w, five 35mm color slides and two contact sheets
    - Mayor's office with school children, behind mayor's desk and SweetHart bus (from Rick Palanzo), Nov 1981 (Box 39.1, Folder 18)
      Two b/w contact sheets
    - JD, AD and Jeff Nahley, posed (Photograph by J. H. Cannatelli), 1981 (Box 39.1, Folder 19)
      One 8x10 b/w photograph
    - Miscellaneous, indoor/outdoor, posed/candids, 1981-1987 (Box 39.1, Folder 20)
      Nine b/w contact sheets
    - Tricentennial, city scenes, 1981-1986 (Box 39.1, Folder 21)
      36 35mm color slides
    - Mayor's office, Jan 1982 (Box 39.1, Folder 22)
      Eight 35mm color slides
    - Danbury Fair Auction, May 1982 (Box 39.1, Folder 23)
      13 3.5x5 color photographs
    - Democratic Clam Bake (JD, Gino Arconti, Toby Moffet, Alice Hyman, William Ratchford, Gov.O'Neill, Jeff Buteara, Joe Walkovich, Wayne Baker), Jul 25, 1982 (Box 39.1, Folder 24)
      17 5x7 b/w, one 3.5x4.5 and one 3.5x5 color, and 4 contact sheets
    - Dedication Westside Classroom Building, Fall 1982 (Box 39.1, Folder 25)
      35mm color slide film
    - Corporate Advisory Board, ca.1983 (Box 39.1, Folder 26)
      Nine 3.5x4 color photographs
    - Grasso Hall Dedication, 1983 (Box 39.1, Folder 27)
      One 8x10 and two 5x7 b/w photographs
    - HVCEO (Housatonic Valley Council of Elected Officials), Sep 1983 (Box 39.1, Folder 28)
      One 4x6 color photograph
    - Ives Street, JD Mayor's office, ca.1983 (Box 39.1, Folder 29)
      One 8x10 b/w contact sheet
    - Old Jail, May 1983 (Box 39.1, Folder 30)
      Four color slides and News-Times Editorial dated 5/3/83
    - JD with Tip O'Neill, Jun 1983 (Box 39.1, Folder 31)
      Two 3.5x5 color photographs with note from William Goodman and Albert Kohn
    - JD, JD/AD, staff, speeches, swearing in ceremony (Ratchford, Lieberman, et al) candids/posed, Nov 1983 (Box 39.1, Folder 32-34)
      143 35mm color slides, two b/w contact sheets and one 5x7 color
    - 40th Birthday Flyer: JD,AD, Fire Chief Bertalovitz (Photographs by A. Corkaptein, Jr.), Nov 1983 (Box 39.1, Folder 35)
      Two 3.5x5, two 5x7 color and one 4x4 b/w photographs
    - Rededication of Superior Court House, 1984 (Box 39.2, Folder 1)
      One 8x10 b/w and three 4x6 color photographs
    - Memorial Day, 1984 (Box 39.2, Folder 2)
      29 35mm color slides
    - Memorial Day, 1984 (Box 39.2, Folder 3)
    - WCSU Graduation: JD giving Peter Glaser his diploma, Jun 1984 (Box 39.2, Folder 4)
      Four 35mm color slides
    - 20th DHS reunion, JD and Ken Fairchild, Jul 1984 (Box 39.2, Folder 5)
      One 3.5x4 color
    - Tricentennial Kick-Off, 1984 (Box 39.2, Folder 6)
      Three 3.5x4.5 color and six 3.5x5 b/w photographs
    - Tricentennial Parade, 1984 (Box 39.2, Folder 7-8)
      35mm color slide film, four 35mm slides, one 5x7 and two 3.5x5 color photographs
    - Danbury Fair Groundbreaking, Aug 1984 (Box 39.2, Folder 9)
      Three 4x6 color photographs
    - Washington Workshops Send-Off Dinner Speaker (labeled with student names), 1984 (Box 39.2, Folder 10)
      One 8x10 b/w photograph and letter from Union Carbide
    - JD with Dan Garamella, 1984 (Box 39.2, Folder 11)
      Two 5x7 photographs and one b/w contact sheet
    - Miscellaneous publicity shots, ca.1985 (Box 39.2, Folder 12)
    - Celebrity breakfast (JD as waiter), 1985 (Box 39.2, Folder 13)
      35mm b/w negatives
    - Election night, swearing in ceremony and party, Nov 1985 (Box 39.2, Folder 14)
      Eight 3.5x5 color photographs w/negatives and one b/w contact sheet
    - City scenes, 1985 (Box 39.2, Folder 15)
      25 35mm color slides
    - Cruz, Jackie with JD, AD, and Peter Glaser, ca.1985 (Box 39.2, Folder 16)
      Various sizes (7x8 to 4x6 color and b/w photographs)
    - AmericanCancer Society Jail-A-Thon, 1985 (Box 39.2, Folder 17)
      One 5x7 b/w and two color polaroid
    - Senior Center, ca.1985 (Box 39.2, Folder 18)
      Two 5x7 color and one 5x7 b/w photographs
    - JD w/William Ratchford (autographed photograph), ca.1985 (Box 39.2, Folder 19)
      One 7x9 b/w photograph
    - JD in Mayor's office (posed), 1986 (Box 39.2, Folder 20)
    - Events unknown (JD/AD, John Rowland, Gov. O'Neill, W. Ratchford and Miss Teenager of Connecticut), 1986-1987 (Box 39.2, Folder 21)
      Three 3.5x5 and three 3.5x4.5 color
    - "Hands Around Danbury" candids/posed, May 1986 (Box 39.2, Folder 22)
      20 35mm color slides, 35mm b/w negatives, two 3.5x5 b/w photograph
    - Seconding Dodd Nomination at State Convention, Jul 1986 (Box 39.2, Folder 23)
      Six 3.5x5 color photographs
    - Groundbreaking, Mixed-Use Redevelopment Project (T. J. Judd photographer), Jul 1986 (Box 39.2, Folder 24-25)
      23 35mm color slides, 13 5x7 b/w and two 5x7 color photographs, four b/w contact sheets
    - JD with Sandy Salvatore, secretary, Aug 1986 (Box 39.2, Folder 26)
      Four 4x6 color photographs
    - JD/AD "with Father Morrisey turned Navy", Sep 1986 (Box 39.2, Folder 27)
      Two 4x6 color photographs
    - JD/AD with Phil Cappozi and Donny Carona, Sep 1986 (Box 39.2, Folder 28)
    - Mall Opening: JD and AD on merry-go-round, Oct 1986 (Box 39.2, Folder 29)
    - D-Day Celebration, Nov 1986 (Box 39.2, Folder 30)
      Ten 3.5x5 color photographs
    - JD/AD Mayor's birthday and WCSU Ball, 1987 (Box 39.2, Folder 31)
      One 4x6 and one 4x5 color photographs
    - Nomination for Mayor: JD, AD, Mary Ann Doran, Zotos, Gerald Krose, Alison Sedney, Ernie Boynton, Janet Butera, Alice Hyman at nomination for Mayor, City (Photographs by T. J. Judd), 1987 (Box 39.2, Folder 32)
      Eight 5x7, one 4x5 and one 5x5 b/w photographs
    - JD: Mayor's office, w/children, city scenes (candids/posed), 1987 (Box 39.2, Folder 33)
      35mm b/w negatives and contact sheets
    - Danbury High School Graduation, Jun 1987 (Box 39.2, Folder 34)
      Five 4x6 color photographs
    - JD/AD: Mayor's office, JD/AD, w/children by Carol Kaliff (candids/posed), Nov 1987 (Box 39.2, Folder 35)
  - Subseries C: Political Memorabilia and Ephemera, RG6.xx___x
    - Campaign pins and matches: 1962-1966 Gov.Dempsey; 1967 Arconti/Ducibella/McNamara; 1967-1969 Arconti for Mayor; 1969 O'Brien for Mayor; 1973 & 1975 Ducibella; 1976 Y.D.A.National Convention; 1977 Costa/Falzone/Shea; Boughton-77; 1979 Paul Garavel; Chris Dodd & James Seamus; Bill Ratchford 1974; Edward M. Kennedy 1972; Chris Dodd 1984. Matches: Ella T. Grasso Inaugural Ball 1979, John S. Monagan ca.1965, Presidenial' Yacht n.d., 1962-1987 (Box 93)
    - Johnson-Humphrey Campaign, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Young Democratic Clubs of Connecticut, 33rd Convention Booklet, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Jefferson-Jackson-Bailey Dinner Programs, 1967-1975 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - City of Danbury Annual Report, 1968-1969, 1974-1975, 1979-1987 (Newspaper Supplements), 1968-1987 (Box OS 9)
    - Humphrey-Muskie Campaign Poster, 1968 (Box OS 12)
    - Humphrey-Muskie Campaign Correspondence, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Eugene McCarthy Campaign, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Danbury Information, 1970-1985 (Box 41, Folder 6-9)
    - Political Miscellany, 1971-1982 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Dyer campaign and political pins, city key ring, and political memorabilia, 1970-1987 (Box 92)
    - Bumper Stickers: Humphrey/Muskie, Carter/Mondale, Udall '76, Johnson/Humphrey, Humphrey, Kenneth P. O'Donnell, McGovern-Schriver/Monagan Congress, Jerry Ford, U. S. Senator Salinger, LBJ-HHH, Re-Elect Tom Dodd Senator, Chris Dodd '76, Humphrey/Muskie, HHH Humphrey, Kennedy in '72, 1972-1985 (Box OS 5)
    - Democratic Fact Book, 1972 (Box 87)
    - Democratic Party Election Memorabilia, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Connecticut Young Dems--Sarasin Info, Campaign '72, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 2-6)
    - "McGovern - President '72" poster, 1972 (Box OS 13)
    - Committees, 1974-1977 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Connecticut Young Democrats Clippings, 1974-1976 (Box 41, Folder 12-14)
    - Connecticut Young Democrats Releases (ALS Ella Grasso), 1974-1977 (Box 41, Folder 15-20)
    - "ELLA" (Ella T. Grasso) Correspondence, clippings, Grasso's death, Jefferson-Jackson-Baily Dinner and Jefferson-Jackson Dinner Dance booklets (ALS Ella Grasso), 1974-1981 (Box 42, Folder 1-4)
    - Name Tags,Membership Cards, Mayor's Cup Golf Outing, Waldorf Astoria Post Cards, etc., 1974-1992 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Danbury High School, Brubacher-Sheathelm Report, 1975 (Box OS 5)
    - Manual of Legislative Procedure for Legislative and Other Governmental Bodies, 1975 (Box 88)
    - Charles A. Ducibella Campaign, 1975-1976 (Box OS 12)
    - Memorial Day Services Program, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - City of Danbury Youth Commission Press Releases, 1975-1976 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Clippings, Youth Commission and Danbury High School Riots; Youth Commission Report on the riots, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 6a)
    - Clippings, 1975-1986 (Box 42, Folder 7-7a)
    - Connecticut Young Democrats Active (Includes ASL by Christopher J. Dodd, Ella Grasso, Toby Moffett,William A. O'Neill, Morris K. Udall), 1975-1978 (Box 42, Folder 8-9)
    - Connecticut Young Democrats Active, List of Officers of the Young Democrats of America and handwritten release, 1975-1978 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Democratic National Committee Position Papers; State and National Platforms; Fifth District Analysis; and, JD 5th Report, 1975-1976 (Box 42, Folder 10-13)
    - House of Representatives, United States (pewter mug), ca.1975 (Box 95)
    - News-Times Voter's Guide, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Seal Of The City of Danbury (6x6 tile), ca.1975 (Box 94)
    - State of Connecticut, House of Representatives Stamp (JD), ca.1975-1975 (Box 94)
  - Subseries D: Politcal Career, RG6.xx___x
    - Canvassing Info '76, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Clippings (assorted reference material), 1976-1978 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Clippings (18 Folio Size Scrapbooks), 1976-1987 (Item 8-26)
    - The Connecticut Democratic State Platform Booklet, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Democratic National Convention Press Guide, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Intern Papers (JD Political Profile), 1976-1979 (Box 44, Folder 1-2)
    - Invitations, 1976-1987 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Mailing Labels/Lists, 1976-1977 (Box 44, Folder 4-5)
    - Miscellaneous (press releases, notes, clippings), 1976-1977 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Resolutions and Certifications, 1976-1984 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Rotary Club of Danbury Guest Speaker (framed), 1976 (Box 96)
    - State Representative Campaign, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 7-8)
    - WCSC Commencement Program, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Boughton Re-Election, 1977-1981 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Carter, Jimmy, Invitation to Guide to Inaugural, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - City of Danbury,Connecticut, Revised Charter, November 8, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Connecticut General Assembly Directory, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 12)